<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on aasthasingh</title>
    <link>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on aasthasingh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Speed up the development with advanced pair programming: GitHub Copilot</title>
      <link>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/github-copilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/github-copilot/</guid>
      <description>Speed up the development with advanced pair programming: GitHub Copilot     Something Microsoft couldn’t get their hands off of, and you probably won’t be able to either!
 Hello technophiles, Welcome to my blog! Read along to know political, technical, and public understandings and viewpoints on the great magical AI algorithm launched this week.
 “Anyone who puts in money at OpenAI can only expect returns 100 times their investment”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolving with BERT: Introduction to RoBERTa</title>
      <link>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/roberta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/roberta/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auto-code generation using GPT-2</title>
      <link>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/code-gpt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/code-gpt2/</guid>
      <description>Auto-code generation using GPT-2    About GPT-2     GPT-2 stands for “Generative Predictive Transformer”. It is an open-source model trained on an over 1.5 Billion parameters for generating the next sequence of text, for a give sequence.
  The GPT-2 has a remarkable and amazing competence to generate texts, much beyond the expectations of conventional language models.
 “Too dangerous to be released.”    A phrase published the press statement by OpenAI to accompany their announcement of the release of their GPT-2 language model in February 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to NumPy</title>
      <link>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/intro-numpy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/intro-numpy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Key Feature extraction from classified summary of a Text file using BERT</title>
      <link>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/text-summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/text-summary/</guid>
      <description>Harnessing the power of BERT embeddings    In this post, I’ll show you how BERT solves a basic text summarization and categorization issue.
About BERT (Bidirectional Encoder Representations from Transformers)     BERT, in a nutshell, is a model that understands how to represent text. You feed it a sequence, and it scans left and right a number of times before producing a vector representation for each word as an output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YOLO: You Only Look Once</title>
      <link>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/yolo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aasthaengg.github.io/posts/yolo/</guid>
      <description>YOLO: You Only Look Once     The “You Only Look Once,” or YOLO, family of models are a series of end-to-end deep learning models designed for fast object detection, developed by Joseph Redmon, et al. and first described in the 2015 paper titled “You Only Look Once: Unified, Real-Time Object Detection.”
 What is YOLO object detection?    YOLO is a deep learning based approach of object detection.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
